[
    {
        "question": "Is HTML a programming language?",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Does CSS stand for Cascading Style Sheets?",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Is JavaScript a statically-typed language?",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Does 'npm' stand for Node Package Manager?",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Is 'git' a centralized version control system?",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Is '===' in JavaScript used for strict equality comparison?",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Can you use 'let' to declare variables that are block-scoped in JavaScript?",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Is React a JavaScript framework?",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Does 'API' stand for Application Programming Interface?",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Python primarily used for front-end web development?",
        "answer": false
    }
]
